<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-06T21:04:17-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Catholic</title><subtitle>Hey this website is for my meme page</subtitle><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Why?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/en/2021/04/06/why.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why?" /><published>2021-04-06T01:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-04-06T01:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/en/2021/04/06/why</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/en/2021/04/06/why.html">&lt;p&gt;Before I begin, if you read past the first sentence, I’ll be thrilled that someone actually took the time out of their day to voluntarily read this. I appreciate you and thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first question to answer on this page is why? Why was this created? What is the purpose of this meme page, this website? What are the goals?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many reasons, personal and other why I wanted to create this site. The main goal is to share the Catholic faith with individuals who are both Catholic and not, and create a place where someone can get a genuine perspective from someone who follows the Catholic Church and subscribes to Catholic moral teachings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of every Catholic mass, the priest tells us “Go forth, the mass has ended”. Go forth, meaning “Go tell the world about the Good News”. This is partially my way of doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is no secret that let alone Catholicism, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewforum.org/2019/10/17/in-u-s-decline-of-christianity-continues-at-rapid-pace/&quot;&gt;Christianity in general is declining by the day&lt;/a&gt;. This rapid shift in participation in Christianity is reflective of the changing social influence the western world is undergoing. Whether you’re reading this as a Catholic worrying about the decline of your faith, or reading this as an atheist, enthused about the numbers in the aforementioned pew research study, I would ask you to consider whether or not this rapid shift in societal thinking is a good thing. For the last 2000 years Christianity (meaning the act of following Christ) has grown from the original Tweleve Apostles, to the early Christians hiding from persecution in the catacombs, to the around 30% of the world’s population today who follows some form of Christianity. Christianity has guided the western world through some of the greatest technological and intellecutal advancements ever. This isn’t to claim that every single intellectual and technological advancement came from Christian thinking, but it is simply to pose the question of whether or not humanity itself is capable of handling this rapid change. Things that are inherently good for humanity and society that generations’ past have taken for granted may be disappearing with the decreasing reliance on Christianity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbsnews.com/news/americans-more-depressed-now-than-decades-ago/&quot;&gt;Americans today are more depressed than ever before&lt;/a&gt;. I’m not going to argue here that the increasing rates of depression are directly linked to a decrease in Christianity; obviously, “correlation does not equal causation”. In all likelihood, there’s numerous factors at play that are at fault for this, however, would it not be logical to ask the quesstion; “What are we doing differently now that we were not doing before?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess after reading these two paragraphs you might assume the goal of this blog and meme page are to convert people to Catholicism, Spanish inquisition style. This is most definitely not the case. In my opinion, Catholicism’s marketing department simply is less than superb, and it needs to do a better job selling itself to the masses. I believe that people who are struggling can find comfort in our faith. I also believe if you can understand the reasoning behind why there are still so many people around the world who follow Catholicism, the temptation to, at minimum, continue digging deeper is irresistable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My other personal motiviations (if you were curious) are to deepen my own faith and also to practice my Italian skills (hopefully all these posts will be written in both English and Italian).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan is to also keep these long form posts on the website, and leave short captions for the Instagram posts. We know that not many people will sit through a 5-10 paragraph long caption on a post.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="en" /><summary type="html">Before I begin, if you read past the first sentence, I’ll be thrilled that someone actually took the time out of their day to voluntarily read this. I appreciate you and thank you!</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="it"><title type="html">Perchè?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/it/2021/04/06/why.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perchè?" /><published>2021-04-06T01:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-04-06T01:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/it/2021/04/06/why</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/it/2021/04/06/why.html">&lt;p&gt;La prima domanda per chiedi è perchè. Perchè sto facendo quello sito, e quello pagina di meme.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="it" /><summary type="html">La prima domanda per chiedi è perchè. Perchè sto facendo quello sito, e quello pagina di meme.</summary></entry></feed>